http://www.notcot.com/about/privacy/

PRIVACY POLICY
Welcome to the NOTEMPIRE: NOTCOT INC's Websites.
We are committed to providing privacy in our products and services. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices. If you give us personal information, we treat it according to this policy, and we use your personal information only in the ways specified when it was collected. We do not otherwise share it.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
Our Websites typically collect two kinds of information about you: (a) information that you provide that personally identifies you; and (b) information that does not personally identify you, that we automatically collect when you visit our Websites.
Personally Identifiable Information:
Our definition of personally identifiable information includes any information that may be used to specifically identify or contact you, such as your name, mail address, phone number, etc. In certain circumstances, we may request, allow or otherwise provide you an opportunity to submit your personally identifiable information in connection with a feature, program, promotion or some other aspect of our Websites. For instance, you may: (a) provide your name/username, password, email address, homepage and bio to register for our Websites, (b) provide your name, mail/shipping address, email address, and phone number in connection with a contest entry or (c) provide certain demographic information about you (e.g., age, gender, purchase preference, usage frequency, etc.) when participating in a survey or poll.
Whether or not you provide this information is your choice; however, in many instances this type of information is required to participate in the particular activity, realize a benefit we may offer, or gain access to certain content.
Non-Personal Information:
Non-personal information can include certain personally identifiable information that has been de-identified; that is, information that has been rendered anonymous. We obtain non-personal information about you from information that you provide us, either separately or together with your personally identifiable information. We also automatically collect certain non-personal information from you when you access our Websites. This information can include, among other things, IP addresses, the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, etc.), the website from which your visit originated, the operating system you are using (e.g., Vista, Windows XP, Mac OS, etc.), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, NetZero, etc.), the search terms you use on our Websites, “clickstream” data that tracks the specific web pages you visit, and the duration of your visits.
HOW WE USE & SHARE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED
Personally Identifiable Information:
The personally identifiable information you submit to us is generally used to carry out your requests, respond to your inquiries, better serve you, or in other ways associated with the circumstances in which you provided the information. We may also use this information to later contact you for a variety of reasons, such as customer service or to communicate with you about content or other information you have posted or shared with us via our Websites.
In certain instances we may also share your personally identifiable information with third party vendors performing functions on our behalf (or on behalf of our affiliated companies) — e.g., deliver our merchandise, administer our promotions, provide us marketing or promotional assistance, analyze our data, assist us with customer service, etc. Our vendors agree to use this information, and we share information with them, only to carry out our requests. In addition, we may share your personally identifiable information with participating sponsors to a program or promotion (e.g., a sweepstakes or contest) you enter via our Websites, and with third parties who assist us in using the content or other information you have posted or shared with us via our Websites (e.g., production companies we may use). Further, we may share your personally identifiable information with third parties such as our co-promotional partners and others with whom we have marketing or other relationships. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use, or as set forth when you submit the information, your personally identifiable information will not be shared or sold to any third parties without your prior approval.
Non-Personal Information:
We use non-personal information in a variety of ways, including to help analyze site traffic, understand customer needs and trends, carry out targeted promotional activities, and to improve our services. We may use your non-personal information by itself or aggregate it with information we have obtained from others. We may share your non-personal information with our affiliated companies and third parties to achieve these objectives and others, but remember that aggregate information is anonymous information that does not personally identify you.
OTHER USES & INFORMATION
IP Addresses:
An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Internet. Web servers (computers that "serve up" web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When visitors request pages from our Websites, our servers typically log their IP addresses. We collect IP addresses for purposes of system administration, to report non-personal aggregate information to others, and to track the use of our Websites. IP addresses are considered non-personal information and may also be shared as provided above. It is not our practice to link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable; that is, the visitor's session will be logged, but the visitor remains anonymous to us. However, we reserve the right to use IP addresses to identify a visitor when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Websites’ rules or to: (a) fulfill a government request; (b) conform with the requirements of the law or legal process; (c) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our Websites, or other users; or (d) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of our Websites' users or the general public.
Cookies, etc.:
"Cookies" are small text files from a website that are stored on your hard drive. These text files make using our Websites more convenient by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. Cookies themselves do not typically contain any personally identifiable information. We may analyze the information derived from these cookies and other technological tools we employ (such as clear gifs/web beacons) and match this information with data provided by you or another party. We may provide our analysis and certain non-personal information to third parties (who may in turn use this information to provide advertisements tailored to your interests), but this will not involve disclosing any of your personally identifiable information. Please note that advertisers that serve advertisements on our Websites may also use their own cookies and other technological tools that are subject to the advertiser's privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy.
If you are concerned about the storage and use of cookies, you may be able to direct your Internet browser to notify you and seek approval whenever a cookie is being sent to your hard drive. You may also delete a cookie manually from your hard drive through your Internet browser or other programs. Please note, however, that some parts of our Websites will not function properly or be available to you if you refuse to accept a cookie or choose to disable the acceptance of cookies.
Email Communications:
If you send us an email with questions or comments, we may use your personally identifiable information to respond to your questions or comments, and we may save your questions or comments for future reference. For security reasons, we do not recommend that you send non-public personal information, such as passwords, social security numbers, or bank account information, to us by email. However, aside from our reply to such an email, it is not our standard practice to send you email unless you request a particular service or sign up for a feature that involves email communications , it relates to purchases you have made with us (e.g., product updates, customer support, etc.), we are sending you information about our other products and services, or you consented to being contacted by email for a particular purpose. In certain instances, we may provide you with the option to set your preferences for receiving email communications from us; that is, agree to some communications but not others. You may "opt out" of receiving future commercial email communications from us by clicking the "unsubscribe" link included at the bottom of any commercial emails we send , or as provided below; provided, however, we reserve the right to send you transactional emails such as customer service communications.
Transfer of Assets:
As we continue to develop our business, we may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or substantially all of our assets, the personally identifiable information and non-personal information we have about you will be transferred to and used by this acquiring entity, though we will take reasonable steps to ensure that your preferences are followed. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, all such information may be considered an asset of ours and as such may be sold or transferred to third parties.
Other:
Notwithstanding anything herein to the contrary, we reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable or non-personal information about you if we are required to do so by law, and/or if we believe that such action is necessary to: (a) fulfill a government request; (b) conform with the requirements of the law or legal process; (c) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our Websites, or other users; or (d) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of our Websites' users or the general public.
Third-party Advertisers
The ads appearing on these Websites are delivered by our advertising partners. They, and the companies they contract with for ad serving, traffic measurement, marketing analytics and ad targeting may place or recognize unique cookies on your browser and use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services. The information collected does not include personally identifiable information like your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number. It does include IP addresses, though these are not tied to individual readers' accounts. You may decline to participate in targeting and other programs employing web usage data via the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool.
Links to Other Sites
These Websites contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by NOTCOT. Please be aware that we, NOTCOT, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by these Website.
Changes in This Privacy Statement
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and to other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
Working on Your Own Privacy Policy?
Check out TRUSTe. Their very useful Model Privacy Disclosures document was one of the resources we tapped in crafting our policies.
Copyright NOTCOT INC 2006-2018. Work in Progress - So be nice.
Privacy Policy
